Guide to the World War II servicemen alumni files, class years 1939-1945.
World War II servicemen alumni files
- Wescott, Karl Warn 1935 (Box 3, Folder 143)
- Wessman, Bertel Stig 1945 (Box 3, Folder 144)
- White, Charles Hulbert 1931 (Box 3, Folder 145)
- White, Robert Edward 1941 (Box 3, Folder 146)
- Whiting, John Talman Jr. 1941 (Box 3, Folder 147)
- Whitman, James Richard 1945 (Box 3, Folder 148)
- Willie, Henry Valentin 1937 (Box 3, Folder 149)
- Wight, Stanley Griswold 1922 (Box 3, Folder 150)
- Wilbur, Francis Cressy 1918 (Box 3, Folder 151)
- Williams, Kenneth (Box 3, Folder 152)
- Wilson, Ian Griffiths 1943 (Box 3, Folder 153)
- Wilson, Ira Washington 1938 (Box 3, Folder 154)
- Wilson, Robert Green 1944 (Box 3, Folder 155)
- Wilson, Wallace Monroe 1929 (Box 3, Folder 156)
- Winters, Joseph Rupert 1928 (Box 3, Folder 157)
- Woehr, Donald Charles 1944 (Box 3, Folder 158)
- Woodward, Reid Talmage (Box 3, Folder 159)
- Wortis, Herman I 1933 (Box 3, Folder 160)
- Wright, John Edmund 1934 (Box 3, Folder 161)
- Wright, James Nichols 1944 (Box 3, Folder 162)
- Youmans, Joseph MacArthur 1932 (Box 3, Folder 163)
- Young, Douglas Mcrae 1936 (Box 3, Folder 164)
- Young, Thomas Sloan Jr. (Box 3, Folder 162)
- Zagata, Joseph Richard 1942 (Box 3, Folder 166)
- Zinke, Irwin L. 1946 (Box 3, Folder 167)